<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Explore Food</string>
    <string name="msm">Emphatically the king of curries, and perhaps the king of all foods. Spicy, coconutty, sweet and savory. Even the packet sauce you buy from the supermarket can make the most delinquent of cooks look like a Michelin potential. Thankfully, someone invented rice, with which diners can mop up the last drizzles of curry sauce. "The Land of Smiles" isnt just a marketing catch-line. Its a result of being born in a land where the worlds most delicious food is sold on nearly every street corner.</string>
    <string name="nape">Spare us the lumpy chain monstrosities and "everything-on-it" wheels of greed. The best pizza was and still is the simple Neapolitan, an invention now protected by its own trade association that insists on sea salt, high-grade wheat flour, the use of only three types of fresh tomatoes, hand-rolled dough and the strict use of a wood-fired oven, among other quality stipulations. With just a few ingredients dough, tomatoes, olive oil, salt and basil (the marinara pizza does not even contain cheese)  the Neapolitans created a food that few make properly, but everyone enjoys thoroughly.</string>
    <string name="choc">The Mayans drank it, Lasse Hallström made a film about it and the rest of us get over the guilt of eating too much of it by eating more of it. The story of the humble cacao bean is a bona fide out-of-the-jungle, into-civilization tale of culinary wonder. Without this creamy, bitter-sweet confection, Valentines Day would be all cards and flowers, Easter would turn back into another dull religious event.</string>
    <string name="sush">When Japan wants to build something right, it builds it really right. Brand giants such as Toyota, Nintendo, Sony, Nikon and Yamaha may have been created by people fueled by nothing more complicated than raw fish and rice, but its how the fish and rice is put together that makes this a global first-date favorite. The Japanese dont live practically forever for no reason they want to keep eating this stuff.</string>
    <string name="ham">When something tastes so good that people spend $20 billion each year in a single restaurant chain devoted to it, you know it has to fit into this list. McDonalds may not offer the best burgers, but thats the point it does not have to. The bread-meat-salad combination is so good that entire countries have ravaged their eco-systems just to produce more cows.</string>
    <string name="peck">The maltose-syrup glaze coating the skin is the secret. Slow roasted in an oven, the crispy, syrup-coated skin is so good that authentic eateries will serve more skin than meat, and bring it with pancakes, onions and hoisin or sweet bean sauce. Other than flying or floating, this is the only way you want your duck.</string>
    <string name="peng">Poached, flaked mackerel, tamarind, chili, mint, lemongrass, onion, pineapple ... one of Malaysia s most popular dishes is an addictive spicy-sour fish broth with noodles (especially great when fused with ginger), that will have your nose running before the spoon even hits your lips.</string>
    <string name="tom">This best food Thai masterpiece teems with shrimp, mushrooms, tomatoes, lemongrass, galangal and kaffir lime leaves. Usually loaded with coconut milk and cream, the hearty soup unifies a host of favorite Thai tastes: sour, salty, spicy and sweet. Best of all is the price: cheap.</string>
    <string name="explore_food">EXPLORE FOOD</string>
    <string name="massaman_curry">Massaman Curry</string>
    <string name="line">________________________________________________________________________________________________________________</string>
</resources>